<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jonathan Rhodes Technical Rider on Jonathan Rhodes</title>
    <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/rider/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jonathan Rhodes Technical Rider on Jonathan Rhodes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jonathanrhodes.nl/rider/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Rhodes Technical Rider</title>
      <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/rider/duo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/rider/duo/</guid>
      <description>Jonathan Rhodes Rider - Duo We&#39;re looking forward to playing at your venue! To prevent any miscommunication, we try to be as thorough as possible. We really appreciate all technicians who make our shows possible and we&#39;re flexible as long as communication is clear. 🤠 Line-up Duo Shows Name Instrument Technical needs Jonathan Lead Vocal Vocal Mic Acoustic Guitar DI (usually brings own DI, but please have on hand) Daniël Backing Vocal Vocal Mic Electric Guitar mic for amp Acoustic Guitar DI PA The venue is expected to provide a quality PA system suitable for the (size of the) venue, capable of amplifying the line-up mentioned above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Rhodes Technical Rider</title>
      <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/rider/full-band/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/rider/full-band/</guid>
      <description>Jonathan Rhodes Rider - Full Band We&#39;re looking forward to playing at your venue! To prevent any miscommunication, we try to be as thorough as possible. We really appreciate all technicians who make our shows possible and we&#39;re flexible as long as communication is clear. 🤠 Line-up Full Band Shows Name Instrument Technical needs Jonathan Lead Vocal Vocal Mic Acoustic Guitar DI (usually brings own DI, but please have on hand) Daniël Backing Vocal Vocal Mic Electric Guitar 2 mics for 2 amps Michaël Bass DI for Ampeg head, mic for cabinet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Rhodes Technical Rider</title>
      <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/rider/small-band/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/rider/small-band/</guid>
      <description>Jonathan Rhodes Rider - Small Band (no drums) We&#39;re looking forward to playing at your venue! To prevent any miscommunication, we try to be as thorough as possible. We really appreciate all technicians who make our shows possible and we&#39;re flexible as long as communication is clear. 🤠 Line-up Small Band Shows Name Instrument Technical needs Jonathan Lead Vocal Vocal Mic Acoustic Guitar DI (usually brings own DI, but please have on hand) Daniël Backing Vocal Vocal Mic Electric Guitar 2 mics for 2 amps Michaël Bass DI for Ampeg head, mic for cabinet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonathan Rhodes Technical Rider</title>
      <link>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/rider/solo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonathanrhodes.nl/rider/solo/</guid>
      <description>Jonathan Rhodes Rider - Solo I&#39;m looking forward to playing at your venue! To prevent any miscommunication, I try to be as thorough as possible. I really appreciate all technicians who make my shows possible and I&#39;m flexible as long as communication is clear. 🤠 Line-up Solo Shows Name Instrument Technical needs Jonathan Lead Vocal Vocal Mic Acoustic Guitar DI (usually brings own DI, but please have on hand) PA The venue is expected to provide a quality PA system suitable for the (size of the) venue, capable of amplifying the line-up mentioned above.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
